https://www.fordogtrainers.com/privacy.html

.
Categories
Super DealsClick To Save MoneyDog Muzzles->Dog Collars->Dog Harnesses->Dog Leashes->Dog Bite SuitsDog
Bite Toys->Dog TreatsDog Bite Tugs->Agitation whipsAgitation sticksDog
Bite Sleeves->FDT Pro ClothingDog Training ClothingDog Training DumbbellsDog Training EquipmentKennel AccessoriesChoose muzzle by breedPictures from customers->Airedale TerrierAkitaAmstaffAmerican BulldogBoxerBullmastiffBull TerrierCane CorsoDobermanDogue De BordeauxEnglish BulldogFrench BulldogGerman ShepherdGreat DaneLabradorMalinoisMastiffNewfoundlandPitbullRottweilerSiberian HuskyStaffordshire TerrierMixed BreedAll dog breeds->Specials ...New Products ...All Products ...
New Products
[more]
*Brandy wearing our exclusive Tracking / Pulling / Agitation Leather Dog Harness For Rottweiler H5$45.00
Important Links
Company's press releases
Useful Info for Dog Owners
How to Choose a Dog Muzzle
How to Choose a Dog Leash
How to Choose a Dog Collar
How to Choose a Dog Harness
Useful Resources
Site map 777
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
ForDogTrainers.comis committed to protecting your privacy online.We do not sell or rent your personal information to outside parties. Any
information we collect is for the purposes of filling orders, contacting
purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information,
enhancing the operation of our site, and for statistical purposes.
Your
information is safe with us.ForDogTrainers.com will not sell, trade or rent youraddress,
e-mail, or accounting informationto any other entity,
no matter how much they twist our arms. Also we will not contact
you, about issues other than an order placed, without your
permission.We use the information you provide
to process orders and to create a more personalized shopping
experience. Unless you specifically and knowingly provide
such information, ForDogTrainers.com will not collect any personal
information about you.It may
be helpful for you to know how we use the information we collect:When
you order, we ask for your name, email address, mailing
address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration
date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order
and to notify you of your order status.When
you sign up for a newsletter or other emailed communication,
we may ask you for your email address so we can send you
the updates and information requested. We do not send
out unsolicited email. You will only receive communication
you have specifically asked for.When
you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for
your name, address and email address so we can administer
the contest and notify winners.We
may collect certain technical information that helps us
to understand our customers' use of the ForDogTrainers.com
web site so that we can make improvements. The information
collected does not allow us to identify you personally.
For example, such information may include the type of
Internet Browser you are using and the pages visited.
This information enables us to improve your experience
at ForDogTrainers.com.By using
our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this
information by ForDogTrainers.com. If you are under 18 years of
age, you must have your parent or guardian's permission to
order.
If you are interested in our policy regarding the use of discount codes, please follow the link below:
Disclaimer
Shopping Cart
[more]
Your cart is empty.
Search
Advanced Search
Information
About Us
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Policy
Links
Contact Us
Site Map
Follow US!
!-- Begin Mailchimp Signup Form -->
NEWSLETTER
Email Address
*
Name
*
Bestsellers
1.   Adjustable Nylon Dog Harness for...
2.   Nylon Dog Harness for Pulling,...
3.   Premium Quality Black Leather Dog...
4.   Lightweight Leather Basket Muzzle...
5.   Wire Basket Dog Muzzle for...
Reviews
[more]
Thank you for your fast sevice , got my New Army bite...I need to be able to have two ratings for this product. The...I Bought this collar for my black lab and I have to say...
Quick LinksHomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsNew ProductsAll Products ...
InformationAbout UsSite MapGift Certificate FAQDiscount CouponsNewsletter Unsubscribe
Customer ServiceContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyLinksMy Account
Important Links
Best choice of dog leashes - dog leashes of any size and for any task - walking leashes, training dog leashes
Dog muzzles for any breed - over 30 sizes available, get dog muzzle now
Dog harnesses - pay less for leather dog harnesses and nylon dog harnesses
Dog harness,Dog muzzle,Dog collar,Dog leashes,Bite Sleeves,Dog Training Equipment. Powered by fordogtrainers.com
